{
    "by": "アクティブパーク",
    "types": [
        {
            "id": "itochan",
            "title": "薦",
            "name": "Hiroki Ito",
            "message": "Clouds are hiding all day long☁️ Say hello at midnight☀︎<br>雲は、朝も昼も夕方も夜も深夜も早朝も隠れています☁深夜00:00は、こんにちはを言おう☀︎",
            "url": true
        },
        {
            "id": "rie",
            "title": "子",
            "name": "Rie",
            "message": "Cheer up!<br>元気出して！（ときどき自分に声かけてます(笑)）",
            "url": true
        },
        {
            "id": "ayumihirono",
            "title": "口",
            "name": "Ayumi Hirono",
            "message": "Shaking hands or claping our hands<br>握手または拍手",
            "url": true
        },
        {
            "id": "yamamoo",
            "title": "音",
            "name": "Yamamoo",
            "message": "come on join us!<br>是非顔出して下さい。来た瞬間から貴方はもうアーティスト",
            "url": true
        },
        {
            "id": "yutoohashi",
            "title": "空",
            "name": "Yuto Ohashi",
            "message": "presentday presenttime<br>プレゼントデイ、プレゼントタイム",
            "url": true
        }
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "Q1",
            "question": "Do you believe in invisible existence?",
            "jp": "目に見えないものの存在を",
            "yes": "yes i do",
            "left": "信じる",
            "no": "no i don't",
            "right": "信じない",
            "left_to": "Q2",
            "light_to": "Q4"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q2",
            "question": "Do you often compare with someone?",
            "jp": "人と比べることある？",
            "yes": "yes i do",
            "left": "ある",
            "no": "no i don't",
            "right": "ない",
            "left_to": "Q6",
            "light_to": "Q3"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q3",
            "question": "Which way do you go?",
            "jp": "どちらに行きますか？",
            "yes": "toward left",
            "left": "左へ",
            "no": "toward right",
            "right": "右へ",
            "left_to": "Q5",
            "light_to": "Q6"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q4",
            "question": "Do you think there is a better place?",
            "jp": "今よりももっといい場所があるとおもう",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q7",
            "light_to": "Q3"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q5",
            "question": "I am at the top of the building. because",
            "jp": "ビルのてっぺん",
            "yes": "want to see the sky",
            "left": "空が見たいから",
            "no": "want to see the clouds",
            "right": "雲が見たいから",
            "left_to": "Q9",
            "light_to": "Q8"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q6",
            "question": "Do you want someone to understand?",
            "jp": "理解してほしいと思う？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q10",
            "light_to": "Q8"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q7",
            "question": "Is there a boundary?",
            "jp": "境い目はあるとおもう",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q6",
            "light_to": "Q11"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q8",
            "question": "What do you imagine when you hear &quot;hachi&quot;?",
            "jp": "『はち』といえば、どちらですか？",
            "yes": "8",
            "left": "8",
            "no": "a bee",
            "right": "蜂",
            "left_to": "Q11",
            "light_to": "Q9"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q9",
            "question": "Let&#039;s go to the park. because",
            "jp": "公園行こ",
            "yes": "want to walk with you",
            "left": "歩きたいから",
            "no": "want to talk with you",
            "right": "話したいから",
            "left_to": "Q13",
            "light_to": "Q10"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q10",
            "question": "Let&#039;s talk! because",
            "jp": "話そ",
            "yes": "my hair has grown",
            "left": "髪が伸びたから",
            "no": "I saw a UFO",
            "right": "UFO見たから",
            "left_to": "Q18",
            "light_to": "Q12"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q11",
            "question": "What color do you like?",
            "jp": "好きな色は、何ですか？",
            "yes": "green",
            "left": "緑",
            "no": "red",
            "right": "赤",
            "left_to": "Q12",
            "light_to": "Q13"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q12",
            "question": "What animal do you like?",
            "jp": "好きな動物は、何ですか？",
            "yes": "cats",
            "left": "猫",
            "no": "a bear",
            "right": "熊",
            "left_to": "Q14",
            "light_to": "Q17"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q13",
            "question": "Did you feel good when you watched the TV program &quot;Hanzawa Naoki&quot;?",
            "jp": "半沢直樹見て、スッキリした？",
            "yes": "yes i did",
            "left": "した",
            "no": "no i didn't / i never saw",
            "right": "してない",
            "left_to": "Q19",
            "light_to": "Q18"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q14",
            "question": "Do you know where it came from?",
            "jp": "どこから来たのかを知っている",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q17",
            "light_to": "Q20"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q15",
            "question": "When do you fell happy?",
            "jp": "幸せを感じるのは？",
            "yes": "when being by myself",
            "left": "ひとりでいるとき",
            "no": "when being with someone",
            "right": "他の人といるとき",
            "left_to": "Q16",
            "light_to": "Q18"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q16",
            "question": "I am",
            "jp": "自分は",
            "yes": "an adult",
            "left": "もうさすがに大人",
            "no": "still a child",
            "right": "まだぜんぜん子供",
            "left_to": "Q20",
            "light_to": "Q22"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q17",
            "question": "What taste of ice cream do youlike?",
            "jp": "何味のアイスが好きですか？",
            "yes": "vanilla",
            "left": "バニラ",
            "no": "green tea",
            "right": "抹茶",
            "left_to": "Q21",
            "light_to": "Q22"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q18",
            "question": "Let&#039;s eat gyoza! because",
            "jp": "餃子食べよ",
            "yes": "it&#039;s sunny",
            "left": "晴れてるから",
            "no": "my stomach tells me so",
            "right": "胃がそう言ってるから",
            "left_to": "Q23",
            "light_to": "Q20"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q19",
            "question": "Do you want to travel abroad soon?",
            "jp": "早く海外旅行に行きたい？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "行きたい",
            "no": "no i don't",
            "right": "行きたくない",
            "left_to": "Q21",
            "light_to": "Q31"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q20",
            "question": "Which do you need?",
            "jp": "聴診器と時計、どちらが必要だと思う",
            "yes": "a stethoscope",
            "left": "聴診器",
            "no": "a watch",
            "right": "時計",
            "left_to": "Q24",
            "light_to": "Q21"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q21",
            "question": "Do you like consuming?",
            "jp": "消費が好き？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "好き",
            "no": "no i don't",
            "right": "好きでない",
            "left_to": "Q27",
            "light_to": "Q24"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q22",
            "question": "What do you think about during a boring meeting?",
            "jp": "つまらない会議の間何を考えている？",
            "yes": "things that want to do",
            "left": "やりたいこと",
            "no": "people who love",
            "right": "好きなひとのこと",
            "left_to": "Q26",
            "light_to": "Q25"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q23",
            "question": "Let&#039;s dig potatoes! because",
            "jp": "じゃがいも掘ろ",
            "yes": "haven&#039;t ever seen a shooting star",
            "left": "流れ星見たことないしさ",
            "no": "want to go to germany",
            "right": "ドイツ行きたいし",
            "left_to": "Q28",
            "light_to": "Q26"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q24",
            "question": "When you open your eyes you will see",
            "jp": "目を開くと",
            "yes": "the sky",
            "left": "空がみえる",
            "no": "some people",
            "right": "人がみえる",
            "left_to": "Q28",
            "light_to": "Q31"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q25",
            "question": "You have a trauma?",
            "jp": "トラウマが",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "ある",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "ない",
            "left_to": "Q32",
            "light_to": "Q26"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q26",
            "question": "Chocolate. because",
            "jp": "チョコレート",
            "yes": "it&#039;s cold",
            "left": "寒いから",
            "no": "the parcel isn&#039;t delivered yet",
            "right": "宅配便が届かないから",
            "left_to": "Q33",
            "light_to": "Q27"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q27",
            "question": "Do you want to go and see this event?",
            "jp": "このイベント見てみたい？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "見たい",
            "no": "not really",
            "right": "特に行きたいと思わない",
            "left_to": "Q30",
            "light_to": "Q30"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q28",
            "question": "Can you sleep in the lighted place?",
            "jp": "明るい場所で眠ることができる",
            "yes": "yes i can",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no i can't",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q29",
            "light_to": "Q31"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q29",
            "question": "In the darkest place you would",
            "jp": "もっとも暗い場所で",
            "yes": "lay down",
            "left": "横たわる",
            "no": "close your eyes",
            "right": "目を瞑る",
            "left_to": "Q41",
            "light_to": "Q30"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q30",
            "question": "Do you often listen carefully?",
            "jp": "耳をそばだてる時ある？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "ある",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "ない",
            "left_to": "Q36",
            "light_to": "Q31"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q31",
            "question": "What taste of ramen noodle do you like?",
            "jp": "どの味のラーメンが好きです？",
            "yes": "Tonkotsu (pork bone broth)",
            "left": "豚骨",
            "no": "salt",
            "right": "塩",
            "left_to": "Q34",
            "light_to": "Q41"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q32",
            "question": "What do you see when you walk?",
            "jp": "歩いているときどこを見てる？",
            "yes": "a person passing by",
            "left": "向こうから来る人",
            "no": "scenery around",
            "right": "周りの景色",
            "left_to": "Q33",
            "light_to": "Q35"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q33",
            "question": "Let&#039;s watch the rising sun! because",
            "jp": "朝日見よ",
            "yes": "saw it on the TV yesterday",
            "left": "昨日テレビで見たから",
            "no": "in the mountain now",
            "right": "今山にいるから",
            "left_to": "Q34",
            "light_to": "Q38"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q34",
            "question": "What do you draw with?",
            "jp": "絵を描く時は、何を持ちますか？",
            "yes": "a pencil",
            "left": "鉛筆",
            "no": "a ballpoint pen",
            "right": "ボールペン",
            "left_to": "Q36",
            "light_to": "Q37"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q35",
            "question": "Do you drink alcohol when you are alone?",
            "jp": "ひとりでも",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "飲む",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "飲まない",
            "left_to": "Q42",
            "light_to": "Q38"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q36",
            "question": "Do you like young people these days?",
            "jp": "最近の若者は好き？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "好き",
            "no": "no i don't",
            "right": "嫌い",
            "left_to": "Q42",
            "light_to": "Q40"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q37",
            "question": "Which do you like?",
            "jp": "どちらが好きですか？",
            "yes": "a pillow",
            "left": "枕",
            "no": "a cushion",
            "right": "クッション",
            "left_to": "Q39",
            "light_to": "Q38"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q38",
            "question": "Let&#039;s go to the book store. because",
            "jp": "__",
            "yes": "just found it",
            "left": "見つけたから",
            "no": "it was on the road",
            "right": "落ちてたから",
            "left_to": "Q45",
            "light_to": "Q42"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q39",
            "question": "MUJI is about?",
            "jp": "無印良品といえば、何ですか？",
            "yes": "curry",
            "left": "カレー",
            "no": "cosmetics",
            "right": "化粧水",
            "left_to": "Q40",
            "light_to": "Q46"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q40",
            "question": "Do you want to buy as much as you can at a 100 yen shop?",
            "jp": "いやというほど100均で買い物したい？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "してみたい",
            "no": "not so much",
            "right": "別にしたくない",
            "left_to": "Q48",
            "light_to": "Q41"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q41",
            "question": "Which prefer if you keep walking?",
            "jp": "歩き続けるならどちらがいい",
            "yes": "in the city",
            "left": "街",
            "no": "in a harbor",
            "right": "港",
            "left_to": "Q45",
            "light_to": "Q43"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q42",
            "question": "The Truth",
            "jp": "本当のこと",
            "yes": "want to know",
            "left": "知りたい",
            "no": "don&#039;t want to know",
            "right": "知りたくない",
            "left_to": "Q46",
            "light_to": "Q44"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q43",
            "question": "When you say &quot;thank you&quot; you feel",
            "jp": "ありがとうと伝えるとき",
            "yes": "embarrassed",
            "left": "照れくさい",
            "no": "happy",
            "right": "嬉しくなる",
            "left_to": "Q47",
            "light_to": "Q46"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q44",
            "question": "Love is all about?",
            "jp": "愛こそ",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "すべて",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "すべてではない",
            "left_to": "Q49",
            "light_to": "Q48"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q45",
            "question": "Let&#039;s go out together. because",
            "jp": "デートしましょう",
            "yes": "the wind brew",
            "left": "風が吹いたから",
            "no": "we like green",
            "right": "緑が好きだから",
            "left_to": "Q50",
            "light_to": "Q49"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q46",
            "question": "Where do you drink melon soda?",
            "jp": "メロンソーダは、どこで飲みますか？",
            "yes": "at a cafe",
            "left": "喫茶店",
            "no": "at karaoke shop",
            "right": "カラオケ屋さん",
            "left_to": "ayumihirono",
            "light_to": "itochan"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q47",
            "question": "Do you think it is okay if you have a day you do nothing?",
            "jp": "なにもしない日があってもいいと思う",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "yutoohashi",
            "light_to": "yamamoo"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q48",
            "question": "Do you think expression is necessary?",
            "jp": "表現って必要？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "必要",
            "no": "no i don't",
            "right": "必要ない",
            "left_to": "yamamoo",
            "light_to": "rie"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q49",
            "question": "If there is a kids base what do you think?",
            "jp": "こども基地と聞いたら",
            "yes": "I want to play there!",
            "left": "遊びたい",
            "no": "I want my kids to play there",
            "right": "遊ばせたい",
            "left_to": "rie",
            "light_to": "itochan"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q50",
            "question": "A excuse",
            "jp": "口実",
            "yes": "I need some",
            "left": "いる",
            "no": "I don&#039;t need it",
            "right": "いらない",
            "left_to": "ayumihirono",
            "light_to": "Q46"
        }
    ]
}